I'm Judah Perez

Carlsbad, CA (951) 204-2080 TYTHIN4@GMAIL.COM https://github.com/judah4

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer industry. Skilled in C#, C++, Asp.Net, .NET Core, Unity3D, and game design. IGDA San Diego Chapter Member.

Experience

August 2017 - PRESENT

Gnarlywood Group, Carlsbad CA - Software Developer

- Programmed and developed warehousing systems using C#, ASP.NET.
- Worked with Vue.js javascript framework for web development frontend.
- Utilized Cloud hosting on Azure.
- Implemented Single Sign On using Auth0.
- Built websites and RESTful Web APIs with high I/O requirements and response times.

April 2014 - August 2017

Enteracloud Solutions, Carlsbad CA - Application Developer

- Programmed and designed internal desktop software, websites, and Client eCommerce connections for Shopify and Magento.
- Designed and built web applications in C# with ASP.NET.
- Managed and utilized SQL Server databases.
- Built solutions for clients business needs.
- Created responsive UI with HTML5, Javascript, JQuery and CSS3.
- Designed and developed RESTful Web APIs.

Education

August 2014 - Graduating May 2018

California State University San Marcos - Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Main courses included data structures, computer architecture, computing theory, physics, digital circuitry, MIPS assembly, and game development. Secondary focus in anthropology including physical, cultural, and Maya archeology. Participated in Association of Computing Machinery club.

August 2011 - May 2014

Palomar College, San Marcos CA - Certificate in Computer Science

General education and computer science classes covering Java, game development, C++, and MASM assembly.